ISAAC FIUZA

Salt Lake City, Utah 84103

Phone: (801)979-4813 | Email: fiuzaisaac@hotmail.com LinkedIn:https://www.linkedin.com/in/isaac-fiuza-2b9104100/ |

Github: https://github.com/ifiuza | Portfolio: https://github.com/ifiuza | Portfolio: https://ifiuza.github.io/portfolio.html

SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer - Graduated from the University of Utah Coding Camp in October 2019.

Associates in C.S from Salt Lake Community College 2015 - Certified in Software Development Currently working at Biofire in Salt Lake City in their IT/Tech Support Department: Upgrading and troubleshooting user's PCs.

Prior Experience in 2018: DELL EMC: Providing Tech Support to Customers and Engineers of Dell EMC (Mostly Latin America).

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript: jQuery, React.

Technologies: JavaScript, jQuery, ReactJS, MongoDB, Express, React, Node, XML, JSON,

AJAX, HTML4/5, CSS3, Bootstrap, MySQL. Firebase.

Multilingual: Spanish, Portuguese and intermediate French.

PROJECTS

Train Scheduler Project - https://ifiuza.github.io/trainscheduler/ https://github.com/ifiuza/trainscheduler/

Train Schedule with user input - Built with JavaScript, jQuery,Bootstrap and Firebase database.

Friend Finder - https://github.com/ifiuza/FriendFinder

basically a dating app. This full-stack site will take in results from your users' surveys, then compare their answers with those from other users. - Built with Node and Express Servers

Clicky Game - https://isaac-clicky-game.herokuapp.com/ https://github.com/ifiuza/clickyGame/

Basically a memory game. Built with React.

Final Project from UofUtah Boot Camp - ForGoodness Cakes https://github.com/julioguzman19/ForGoodnessCakes/tree/isaac

A Website made for a bakery. - Used React and MongoDB.

EXPERIENCE

Technical Support Specialist- Help Desk **Biofire Diagnostics**

2019 – Present Salt Lake City, UT

• Follow provided documentation to provision new Windows 10 Computers • Follow provided documentation to perform in place upgrades from Windows 7 to Windows 10 • Utilize provided checklists to ensure computer setup accuracy • Troubleshooting of failed in place upgrades.

Schedule and Dispatch - Customer Service and Tech Support **Dell EMC**

2017 – 2018 Salt Lake City, UT

• English, Spanish and Portuguese Customer Service • Support for Customers and Engineers of Dell EMC • Escalations as Needed •, Scheduling Technicians to Resolve Issues to end users

Car Salesman, Finance Manager, Car buyer Fiuza Motors LLC

2007 – 2017 Salt Lake City, UT

• Purchase dealership inventory through online auctions • Maintain inventory records with Microsoft Excel • Extensive reporting/Data Entry Finance Manager • Maintained records for dealership inventory, car sales (averaging 60 sales per month), and customers with DealerTrack software

EDUCATION

Bootcamp Certificate: University of Utah, Salt Lake City, UT

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & ReactJS.

Associates in CS - Salt Lake Community College, Salt Lake City, UT

Associate of Science in Computer Science and Information Systems: Studied software development (Java language) and Computer Essentials (Microsoft Office, Linux, MySQL, HTML, PHP, JavaScript)